Guide to the Jim Neu Papers MSS.332
Fales Library and Special Collections
- S. Clarinet, TV Speech, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0132)
- Sample Tapes, undated (Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0041, 332.0129)
- Saxophone, undated (Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0058, 332.0109, 332.0182)
- See It / Believe It orig., undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0156)
- Sh'Rell Bass Line, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0094)
- Short Scenes by Jim Neu, 1991-2008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Short Stories and Other Writings by Jim Neu, 1993-1999 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Situation Room, 1988-1991; cuid39271 (Box 21, Folder 7, Box 22, Folder 1-2, Box 29, Audiocassette 332.0037, Box 33, Vhs 332.0232, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_332_ER_28)
- SK/Irene, Oppenheim KPFA Radio, Byrd Talk, 1977 (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0134)
- Snowman Serenade, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0152, Box 33, Vhs 332.0283, Box Shared Fales 043, Folder 26)
- Spin Cycle and Ahhh, Zurich, undated (Box Shared Fales 043, Folder 27)
- Soho Repertory Theater, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Songs Project, undated (Box 22, Folder 4, Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0102, Box Shared Fales 096, Folder 24)
- Spacemen 88 - Clark Terry, 1988 (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0091)
- Splatter!, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 7)
- Stam Getz Interview, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 332.0015)
- Storm Opening #1, undated (Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0010)
- Star Motel, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Straightman, 1982-1985; cuid39272 (Box 22, Folder 7-9, Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0009, 332.0034, 332.0084, 332.0117, 332.0186, 332.0306, Box 33, Vhs 332.0291, Box 35, U-matic 332.0189, 332.0196, 332.0206, 332.0209, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_332_ER_29)
- Sun Ra Memorial, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0044, 332.0183)
- Sunspots (Charles Borkhuis), 1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Tape #2 B Voices // Pee Wee Russell, 1981 (Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0002)
- Tape Delay Dance Solo, 1977 (Box 29, Audiocassette 332.0077)
- Target Audience, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 1-4, Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0069, 332.0124, Box 31, Minidv 332.0308, 332.0311, 332.0314, Box Shared Fales 043, Folder 28)
- Target Audience, 2003-2004; cuid39276 (Box 34, Vhs 332.0242-332.0243, 332.0247, 332.0258, 332.0262, 332.0278, Box 33, Vhs 332.0248, 332.0242-332.0243, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_332_ER_30)
- Theatre Communications Group Inc. (TCG), 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- This Object (film by Jacob Burkhardt, screenplay by Jim Neu), 1982 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- This Object (written by sk dunn), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 6)
- Tribute to Jim Neu at La MaMa, 2010; cuid39275 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_332_ER_31)
- True Comedy Theatre Company -- The True Comedy Planet Newsletter, 1988-1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- TV, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 332.0043)
- Two Conversations with Edwin Denby (features Jim Neu), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Undercurrent Incorporated, 1994, 1998-2000; cuid39273 (Box 23, Folder 8-9, Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0128, Box 31, Minidv 332.0312, Box 34, Vhs 332.0237, 332.0239, 332.0290, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_332_ER_32)
- The Underparty, undated (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
- Unknown and Unfinished Scripts, 1976-1993 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
- Untitled, undated (Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0004, 332.0167, Box 31, Sound disc-minidisc 332.0320, Box 35, U-matic 332.0192, 332.0210)
- Various Short Scenes, 1991-2006 (Box 24, Folder 5-6, Box 35, U-matic 332.0188,332.0190, 332.0214, 332.0216)
- Water Lapping, undated (Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0005)
- Westbeth, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 332.0029)
- Wordsong, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0088)
- The Wrong Mistake, 1993; cuid39274 (Box 25, Box 28, Audiocassette 332.0062, 332.0071, Box 34, Vhs 332.0245, 332.0267, 332.0297, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_332_ER_33)
- The Wrong Tango, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 332.0120)